fullfocusstore.com 2018-06-20

# Privacy Policy – The Full Focus Store by Michael Hyatt and Co.

Full Focus Store™ (“Company,” “we,” or “us”) respects your privacy and is committed to protecting it through this Privacy Policy.

This Privacy Policy governs your access to and use of  
www.fullfocusstore.com, including any content, functionality and services  
offered on or through www.fullfocusstore.com (the "Website"), whether as a  
guest or a registered user.

When accessing the Website, we will learn certain information about you,  
both automatically and through voluntary actions you may take, during your  
visit. This policy applies to information we collect on the Website and in  
email, text, or other electronic messages between you and the Website.

Please read the Privacy Policy carefully before you start to use the  
Website. By using the Website or by clicking to accept or agree to the  
Terms of Use when this option is made available to you, you accept and  
agree to be bound and abide by the Privacy Policy. Through the use of  
www.fullfocussstore.com you are herein consenting to the following data  
procedures expressed within this agreement.

### Children Under The Age Of 13

Our Website is not intended for children under 13 years of age. No one  
under age 13 may provide any information to or on the Website. We do not  
knowingly collect personal information from children under 13. If you are  
under 13, do not use or provide any information on this Website or on or  
through any of its features/register on the Website, make any purchases  
through the Website, use any of the interactive or public comment features  
of this Website or provide any information about yourself to us, including  
your name, address, telephone number, email address, or any screen name or  
user name you may use.

If we learn we have collected or received personal information from a child  
under 13 without verification of parental consent, we will delete that  
information. If you believe we might have any information from or about a  
child under 13, please contact us at [support@fullfocusstore.com](mailto:support@fullfocusstore.com).

### Information We Collect About You

When you access the Website, the Company will learn certain information  
about you during your visit. The Website provides various places for users  
to provide information. We collect information that users provide by  
filling out forms on the Website, communicating with us via contact forms,  
providing comments or other feedback, and providing information when  
ordering a product via the Website.

We use information you provide to us to provide the service and/or deliver  
the requested product, to improve our overall performance, and to provide  
you with offers, promotions, and information.

### Information We Collect Through Automatic Data Collection Technology.

As you navigate through our Website, we may use automatic data collection  
technologies including Google Analytics to collect certain information  
about your equipment, browsing actions, and patterns. This will generally  
include information about your location, your traffic pattern through our  
website, and any communications between your computer and our Website.  
Among other things, we will collect data about the type of computer you  
use, your Internet connection, your IP address, your operating system, and  
your browser type.

The information we collect automatically is used for statistical data and  
will not include personal information. We use this data to improve our  
Website and our service offerings. To the extent that you voluntarily  
provide personal information to us, our systems will associate the  
automatically collected information with your personal information.

### Use of Cookies And Pixels

Similar to other commercial websites, our website utilizes a standard  
technology called “cookies” and server logs to collect information about  
how our site is used. Information gathered through cookies and server logs  
may include the date and time of visits, the pages viewed, time spent at  
our site, and the websites visited just before and just after our own, as  
well as your IP address.

A cookie is a very small text document, which often includes an anonymous  
unique identifier. When you visit a website, that site’s computer asks your  
computer for permission to store this file in a part of your hard drive  
specifically designated for cookies. Each website can send its own cookie  
to your browser if your browser’s preferences allow it, but (to protect  
your privacy) your browser only permits a website to access the cookies it  
has already sent to you, not the cookies sent to you by other sites.

The Company reserves the right to use technological equivalents of cookies,  
including social media pixels. These pixels allow social media sites to  
track visitors to outside websites so as to tailor advertising messages  
users see while visiting that social media website. The Company reserves  
the right to use these pixels in compliance with the policies of the  
various social media sites.​

### International Transfer

Your information, including Personal Information, may be transferred to —  
and maintained on — computers located outside of your state, province,  
country or other governmental jurisdiction where the data protection laws  
may differ than those from your jurisdiction. If you are located outside  
United States and choose to provide information to us, please note that we  
transfer the information, including Personal Information, to the United  
States and process it there. Your consent to this Privacy Policy followed  
by your submission of such information represents your agreement to that  
transfer.

### Links To Other Sites

Our Service may contain links to other sites that are not operated by us.  
If you click on a third party link, you will be directed to that third  
party's site. We strongly advise you to review the Privacy Policy of every  
site you visit.

We have no control over, and assume no responsibility for the content,  
privacy policies or practices of any third party sites or services.

### Email Information

If you choose to correspond with us through email, we may retain the  
content of your email messages together with your email address and our  
responses. We provide the same protections for these electronic  
communications that we employ in the maintenance of information received  
online, mail, and telephone. This also applies when you register for our  
website, sign up through any of our forms using your email address or make  
a purchase on this site. For further information see the email policies  
below.

### Email Policies

We are committed to keeping your e-mail address confidential. We do not  
sell, rent, or lease our subscription lists to third parties, and will not  
disclose your email address to any third parties except as allowed in the  
section titled Disclosure of Your Information.

We will maintain the information you send via e-mail in accordance with  
applicable federal law.

In compliance with the CAN-SPAM Act, all e-mails sent from our organization  
will clearly state who the e-mail is from and provide clear information on  
how to contact the sender. In addition, all e-mail messages will also  
contain concise information on how to remove yourself from our mailing list  
so that you receive no further e-mail communication from us.

Our emails provide users the opportunity to opt-out of receiving  
communications from us and our partners by reading the unsubscribe  
instructions located at the bottom of any e-mail they receive from us at  
anytime.

Users who no longer wish to receive our newsletter or promotional materials  
may opt-out of receiving these communications by clicking on the  
unsubscribe link in the e-mail.

### ​How And Why We Collect Information

The Company collects your information in order to record and support your  
participation in the activities you select. We use this information to  
track your preferences and to keep you informed about the products and  
services you have selected to receive and any related products and/or  
services. As a visitor to this Website, you can engage in most activities  
without providing any personal information. It is only when you seek to  
download resources and/or purchase products that you are required to  
provide information.

If you are outside the European Union and opt to receive any free  
resources, participate in any free training programs, register for a  
webinar, register for a live event, register for a seminar, or purchase any  
products sold by the Company on this Website, we will automatically enroll  
​you to receive our promotional email communications, including our weekly  
magazine. If you do not wish to receive this communication, you can  
unsubscribe anytime. We include an “unsubscribe” link at the bottom of  
every email we send. If you ever have trouble unsubscribing, you can send  
an email to support@fullfocusstore.com requesting to unsubscribe from future emails.

If you are in the European Union and opt to receive any free resources,  
participate in any free training programs, register for a webinar, register  
for a live event, register for a seminar, or purchase any products sold by  
the Company on this Website, we will only enroll you to receive our free  
email communication if you affirmatively consent to it. If you do not wish  
to receive this communication, you can unsubscribe anytime. We include an  
“unsubscribe” link at the bottom of every email we send. If you ever have  
trouble unsubscribing, you can send an email to [support@fullfocusstore.com](mailto:support@fullfocusstore.com)  
requesting to unsubscribe from future emails.

### How Do We Use the Information That You Provide to Us?

We use personal information for purposes of presenting our Website and its  
contents to you, providing you with information, providing you with offers  
for products and services, providing you with information about your  
subscriptions and products, carrying out any contract between you and the  
Company, administering our business activities, providing customer service,  
and making available other items and services to our customers and  
prospective customers.

From time-to-time, we may use the information you provide to us to make you  
offers to purchase products and services provided by third parties in  
exchange for a commission to be paid to us by such third parties. Should  
you opt to take part in such promotions, the third parties will receive  
your information.

From time-to-time, we may use the information you provide to us to display  
advertisements to you that are tailored to your personal characteristics,  
interests, and activities.

### Disclosure Of Your Information

As a general rule, we do not sell, rent, lease or otherwise transfer any  
information collected whether automatically or through your voluntary  
action.

We may disclose your personal information to our subsidiaries, affiliates,  
and service providers for the purpose of providing our services to you.

We may disclose your personal information to a third party, including a  
lawyer or collection agency, when necessary to enforce our terms of service  
or any other agreement between you and the Company.

We may disclose information when legally compelled to do so, in other  
words, when we, in good faith, believe that the law requires it or for the  
protection of our legal rights or when compelled by a court or other  
governmental entity to do so.

### How Do We Protect Your Information and Secure Information Transmissions?

The security of your Personal Information is important to us, and we strive  
to implement and maintain reasonable, commercially acceptable security  
procedures and practices appropriate to the nature of the information we  
store, in order to protect it from unauthorized access, destruction, use,  
modification, or disclosure. However, please be aware that no method of  
transmission over the internet, or method of electronic storage is 100%  
secure and we are unable to guarantee the absolute security of the Personal  
Information we have collected from you.

We employ commercially reasonable methods to ensure the security of the  
information you provide to us and the information we collect automatically.

Email is not recognized as a secure medium of communication. For this  
reason, we request that you do not send private information to us by email.  
However, doing so is allowed, but at your own risk. Credit Card information  
and other sensitive information is never transmitted via email.

The Company may use software programs to create summary statistics, which  
are used for such purposes as assessing the number of visitors to our site,  
what information is of most and least interest, determining technical  
design specifications, and identifying system performance or problem areas.

For site security purposes and to ensure that this service remains  
available to all users, the Company uses software programs to monitor  
network traffic to identify unauthorized attempts to upload or change  
information, or otherwise cause damage.

### Policy Changes

It is our policy to post any changes we make to our privacy policy on this  
page. If we make material changes to how we treat our users' personal  
information, we will notify you by email to the email address specified in  
your account and/or through a notice on the Website home page. The date the  
privacy policy was last revised is identified at the bottom of the page.  
You are responsible for ensuring we have an up-to-date active and  
deliverable email address for you, and for periodically visiting our  
Website and this privacy policy to check for any changes.

### Visitors’ GDPR Rights

If you are within the European Union, you are entitled to certain  
information and have certain rights under the General Data Protection  
Regulation. Those rights include:

We will retain the any information you choose to provide to us until the  
earlier of: (a) you asking us to delete the information, (b) our decision  
to cease using our existing data providers, or (c) the Company decides that  
the value in retaining the data is outweighed by the costs of retaining it.

You have the right to request access to your data that the Company stores  
and the rights to either rectify or erase your personal data.

You have the right to seek restrictions on the processing of your data.

You have the right to object to the processing of your data and the right  
to the portability of your data.

To exercise these rights please email us at [support@fullfocusstore.com](mailto:support@fullfocusstore.com).

To the extent that you provided consent to the Company’s processing of your  
personal data, you have the right to withdraw that consent at any time,  
without affecting the lawfulness of processing based upon consent that  
occurred prior to your withdrawal of consent.

You have the right to lodge a complaint with a supervisory authority that  
has jurisdiction over issues related to the General Data Protection  
Regulation.

We require only the information that is reasonably required to enter into a  
contract with you. We will not require you to provide consent for any  
unnecessary processing as a condition of entering into a contract with us.

### Contact Us

The Company welcomes your questions or comments regarding the Privacy  
Policy:

Michael Hyatt & Company, LLC  
P.O. Box 1221  
Franklin, TN 37065

Email Address: [support@fullfocusstore.com](mailto:support@fullfocusstore.com)

Effective as of May 22, 2018
